mcent.com 2015-02-15

# Privacy - mCent

## Privacy Policy

Effective September 3, 2010

This privacy statement describes how Jana Mobile, inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.mcent.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

  * Collection and Use of Personal Information
  * Choice/Opt-Out
  * Information Sharing
  * Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
  * Security
  * Additional Policy Information
  * Contact Information

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

We also collect the following information from you: 

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type Demographic information such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to: 

* Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
* Send you requested product or service information
* Administer your account
* Send you a newsletter
* Send you marketing communications
* Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
* Respond to your questions and concerns
* Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
* Conduct research and analysis
* Display content based upon your interests
* Enable you to post your resume, search job postings, and contact or be contacted by prospective employers
* List you in our member directory made available only to other members

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you may unsubscribe on your account settings.

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

### Information Obtained from Third Parties

We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.

We purchase marketing data about our customers from third parties and combine it with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products.

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Jana Mobile, inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
  * other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

### Web beacons

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Jana Mobile, inc.. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us here.

### Additional Policy Information

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, please check your account settings.

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

Jana Mobile, Inc.  
141 Tremont St. #4  
Boston, MA, United States 02111
